Hoang Van Nam

Intern Back-end Developer

→ +035 776 3553 (a) namnam290703@gmail.com

CAREER GOALS

Apply the knowledge you have learned into practice, experience challenges at work and work with your passion. Develop and improve your programming skills to become a professional programmer. Desire to work in a dynamic, creative environment, with opportunities to learn and develop professionally.

During your internship, try to accumulate knowledge and skills and develop into an official employee position. And 2 years later, I became a leader, leading the next generation to develop themselves and consolidate the company's development.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Database: SqlSever, MySql.
- Backend: C#, PHP, Java, JavaScript, .NET.
- Frontend: HTML, CSS,Windows Forms, JavaSwing.
- Framework: Entity Framework.

EDUCATION

HANOI COLLEGE OF INDUSTRIAL ECONOMICS (Vietnam)

06/2021 - 06/2024

- Learn about software and websites
- GPA 8.3

WORK EXPERIENCE

HANOI COLLEGE OF INDUSTRIAL ECONOMICS

12/2023 - 01/2024

Human resource management system

- Position: Programmer
- Number of members: 1 person.
- Job Description: Building a human resources management system for a pharmaceutical company, using Visual Studio tool to create WindowsForm interface, code other functions of the system.
- Technology used: Windows Form, C#, SqlSever.
- Result :
- Build human resource management system software.
- The project was evaluated well by the examination board.

NACENCOMM card technology company

02/2024 - 04/2024

Build a sales website

- Position: Programmer
- Number of members: 1 person.
- Job Description: Build a sales website using Visual Studio tools to create the website interface and code other

system functions.

● Technology used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript,Bootstrap,C#,Asp.Net MVC

- Result :
- Successfully built sales website interface
- Respond well to customer feedback requests

CERTIFICATE

• English certificate: B1.

PARTICIPATING PROJECTS

Human resource management of ECO company

(12/2023 - 1/2024)

Customer	Employee
Description	Software to manage all human resources issues for ECO pharmaceutical company
Number of members	1
Position	FrontEnd Developer,BackEnd Developer
Role	-Review design -Setup environment -Code interface(Windows Form) and function(for the user interacts with the software) -Fulfill requests for feedback from users -Fix bugs
Technology	.NET Framework, C#,SQL Sever

Shoe store

(02/2024 -)

Customer	Client
Description	Website provides shoe products to customers
Number of members	1
Position	FrontEnd Developer,BackEnd Developer
Role	-System design analysis -Website design using html, css,bootstrap,javascrip -Using Asp.NET technology on the website with the MVC model coded in C# language to retrieve data information from customers -Stores data and information in SQL Server database -Fulfill requests for feedback from users
Technology	.NET Framework,C#,SQL Sever,

HOBBIES

- Read stories
- Listen to music
- Gaming